m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：冰蓝  阿蘅阿蘅  猫中之王  独醉
校对：念念不忘YY猫  必有回响赛太公   总监   YY
后期：孤帆    时间轴：chaXser
老爸老妈浪漫史
第八季  第十四集
各位  刚才发生的事太神奇了
You guys. You guys will not believe what just happened.
我过来时  一辆出租车撞上人行道的路缘
On my way here, a taxi jumped the curb
压住了一位老太太
and it pinned this old lady,
我马上过去帮忙  开启了大力士模式
and I-I just went into this, like, crazy adrenaline mode
把车从她身上抬了起来
and I somehow lifted it off her.
天啊  泰德  你的手腕
Oh, my God, Ted, your wrist.
对哦  是有点肿了
Oh, yeah, I guess it's a little swollen.
-肯定是抬车时拉伤了  -不
- I must've strained it lifting. - No,
我觉得亲爱的莉莉指的是
I believe our dear friend Lily was referring
你另外一只手腕
to your other wrist.
带着男性节育环的那只
The one wearing the male birth control.
一般节育环是放置于女性子宫内部
我本来准备说"婚前禁欲手镯"的
I was gonna go with "Chastity bracelet."
这种手镯一般只是信基督教的女人才戴
天啊  还能更爱你吗
God, is it possible to love you more?
真的假的  我刚才救了别人一命
Really? Really? I just saved someone's life,
而你们关注的重点竟然是这个
and you guys are focusing on this?
就是  各位  不要嘲笑他了
Yeah, you know what, guys? Leave him alone.
他是个英雄
All right, he's a hero.
谢谢
Thank you.
你觉得你有超能力是因为
Do you think that your super strength came from
戴着神奇女侠的魔力护腕吗
wearing Wonder Woman's magic wrist cuff?
我告诉你们  因为这个护腕
Yeah, I'll have you know that because of this cuff,
我有了个约会
I have a date.
是跟护手霜和互联网约"打飞机"吗
With some hand lotion and the Internet?
原来真的可以更爱你
It is possible to love you more!
是跟真人约会
She exists.
她就在酒吧外
And she's right outside.
太好了  带她进来啊
Great. Bring her in.
其实外面天气很好
You know what? It's so nice out.
我们何不出去散散步
Why don't... why don't we just all go for a walk.
外面下倾盆大雨呢  泰德
It's pouring rain, Ted.
显然是她太胖  进不了酒吧的门
I think it's pretty obvious she can't fit through the door.
她是个漂亮的运动型姑娘
She is a gorgeous, athletic woman.
"运动型"  浓鬓角没胸部
"Athletic"? Sideburns, no cans.
她是辣妹
She is hot.
那她为什么不能进来  泰德
So why can't she come in, Ted?
她当然能进来
She can come in.
再等六个半月后就能了
In six and a half months.
等等  你是在说她今年...
Wait. Are you saying she's...
二十岁
Twenty.
半
And a half.
左右
Almost.
等等  各位
Hold up, guys.
她得闪了
She had to bounce.
因为有一群快闪族出现在
Um, a flash mob broke out in front
威廉斯堡的一排墨西哥韩式快餐车前
of a line of Korean-Mexican food trucks in Williamsburg.
唯一能让她更像20岁姑娘的东西是
The only thing that would make her more of a 20-year-old
她搞笑的交通工具
is an ironic form of transportation.
她穿着轮滑鞋
She's roller skating there.
我不知道哪件事更可悲
I don't know which is more pathetic--
是你和二十岁的小妞约会
that you're going out with a 20-year-old
还是你为了和她约会买了个皮质护腕
or that you bought a leather cuff to get a date with her.
我又不是因为她才买这个
I didn't buy this to get a date.
只是碰巧赶上
I just happened to be out
我周六下午出门
catching up on some Saturday afternoon
选购皮质护腕
leather cuff shopping,
而她  碰巧是卖皮质护腕的妹子
and she just happened to be a leather cuff saleswoman.
天啊  真庆幸我的泡妞生涯结束了
God, I am so glad I am done chasing bimbos.
现在我订婚了  过去泡妞的生活
Now that I'm engaged, that whole part of my life
看起来可悲又空洞
just seems sad and empty.
我不是故意要说得这么难听
I don't want this to sound too harsh,
泰德  但是你让我恶心
Ted, but you disgust me.
一个月前  你家床头板上还有润滑油机呢
Until a month ago, your headboard had a lube dispenser.
对
Uh, yeah.
-我们把它扔了  -对
- We got rid of that, okay? - Yeah.
说到订婚
Anyway, speaking of engaged,
快瞧什么东西改好尺寸啦
check out what got back from being resized.
天啊  好大一颗钻石
Oh, my God. Look at the size of that rock.
巴尼  你不能一开始就买
Barney, you don't start with
一颗"偷情赎罪级"的大钻石
the I-got-caught-cheating diamond.
你得给自己留点发展空间啊
You give yourself room to grow.
这是传家宝
It's a family heirloom.
圣诞节期间
Yeah, I got a few dirty looks
巴尼的嫂子一直对我甩白眼
from Barney's half-sister over Christmas,
所以我请她坐下  然后毕恭毕敬地解释
so I had to sit her down and explain very respectfully...
让她羡慕嫉妒恨吧
that she can suck it.
好吧  我得闪了
Okay. I got to bounce.
别这样说
Stop saying that.
迪拜来的DJ在布什维克
This DJ from Dubai is spinning
一个废弃的装货码头打碟
at an abandoned loading dock in Bushwick.
我担心我衣服穿少了会冷
I'm worried I don't have enough layers.
就算我朋友们都不看好又怎样
So what if my friends thought it was doomed?
我当时还年轻
I was still young,
知道和比我小十岁的姑娘
and I knew that a night of partying with a girl
狂欢一晚  完全是一场...
over a decade younger than me would be a total...
灾难
...disaster.
她和我简直是两个世界的人
She's like an entirely different species.
而且我衣服绝对穿少了
And I definitely didn't have enough layers.
她说的词语  我一半都听不懂
I didn't understand half the words she was saying.
我听起来都像嬉皮士版的填词游戏
To me, it all sounded like hipster Mad Libs.
你没看手机吗
Didn't you check your phone?
我刚在"目前很热的社交网站"上
I just "means of contacting" you
"联系"了你
on "currently hot social networking site."
表演改到
The show's been moved
"你从未听说过的纽约郊区"去了
to "New York neighborhood you've never heard of."
我的手机上居然会显示时间
Oh. Wow, my phone has a clock.
而且他们很爱吃超怪异的混合风食品
And they subsist on a diet of pointlessly weird combinations.
你要不要跟我分吃个泡菜小蛋糕
Hey, do you want to split a kimchi cupcake
上面有培根糖霜哦
with bacon frosting?
这是最美味的搭配
They are the best here.
好啊  跟我的黄瓜胡椒蛋蜜乳
Uh, yeah. Yeah, that'll go great with my
估计也会很搭吧
cucumber jalapeno egg cream.
快喝  快点  快点
Chug it! Come on. Come on.
-我们得走了  -好吧
- We got to get going. - Right. Okay.
然后  在唐人街
Then later, at a club in Chinatown
井盖下的一个酒吧
somehow located beneath a manhole cover,
事情变得很诡异
it got weird.
天啊  我真喜欢
God, I just love those
你眉毛里的小灰毛
tiny gray hairs in your eyebrows.
老人好性感
Old men are so sexy.
好了  公平地说
All right, to be fair,
有些小灰毛其实是干了的蛋蜜乳
some of those gray hairs were dried egg cream.
原来一边溜冰一边呕吐
Turns out, when you projectile vomit on skates,
吐出来的东西会直接溅你一脸
you roll right into the spray.
她到底觉得你有多老
Wait, how old does she think you are?
你去越南参战了吗[1959年-1975年]
So, were you in Vietnam?
等等再叹息
Hold that groan.
越共无所不在啊
Charlie was everywhere.
她是辣妹  喜欢老人
She's hot! She likes old guys!
别批判我
Don't judge me!
总之  当我们进入舞池时
Anyway, when we got out on the dance floor, th...
我发誓  二十岁的人就是这个样子
I swear, this is what all the 20-year-olds looked like...
谢谢你对国家做出的贡献  士兵
I want to thank you for your service to this nation, Private.
是上校
Colonel.
我得做个了断
I got to end this.
没错  说真的  泰德
Yeah, seriously, Ted.
假扮别人  骗妞上床
Pretending to be someone else just to get laid?
那  太尴尬了
That's... embarrassing.
殿下
Your Highness!
我们走
Let's go.
马修  把护腕脱了
Ew. Marshall, take that off.
为什么  我觉得挺酷的
What? I think it looks kind of cool.
酷
Cool?
你看就像某个烂乐队的小混混
You look like one of those jerks who's in some lame band
骑摩托车不带头盔
and rides a motorcycle without a helmet
腰上挂着钱包链  脖子上有纹身
and has a wallet chain and neck tattoos
还爱吸毒
and a drug problem.
毒瘾不是很大
Not a... a big one, just, uh...
但也够让他暗地里贩贩毒
enough that he deals a little bit on the side, and...
他绝不会对女人动真情
he can never... ever be true to one woman.
快把你的咸菜吃完  开"干"了
Finish that damn pickle and do me!
你们都知道我的早晨通常是怎样的吧
Okay, you guys know how my mornings usually go.
我们不想知道
Why would we care how...
通常是这样的
Usually it's like this.
你先
After you.
谢谢
Aw, thank you.
送你的  罗宾
On the house, Robin!
贝果圈送你 *
* Take this bagel on the house
报纸送你 *
* Have a paper on the house
只要你愿意 *
* I'd give you a house on the house
房子也可送你 *
* If I could
沉鱼落雁之姿 *
* You're so beautiful
世间万物皆可送你 *
* Everything in life should be free
做自己感觉真美好 *
* It's so wonderful to be me!
知更鸟也会在早上帮你更衣吗
Do little bluebirds help you get dressed in the morning, too?
她只是夸张地表达观点 *
* She's exaggerating to make a point!
但是今天一切都变了
But today was different.
3.75元
That'll be $3.75.
我昨天就没付钱啊
But I didn't have to pay yesterday.
好吧  那就7.5元
Okay. $7.50.
-我亲爱的乖乖  -是戒指  罗宾
- Oh, honey-sweetie-baby. - It's the ring, Robin.
那戒指有魔力
The ring has power.
当女人戴上订婚戒指时
When a woman puts on an engagement ring,
就像《指环王》哈比人中比尔博・巴金斯
it's like when Bilbo Baggins wears the One Ring
戴上至尊魔戒一样
in The Hobbit.
这么宅男的解释我听不懂
Okay, can you say that again but not in nerd?
好吧  戒指就像哈利波特
Sure. Uh, the ring is like the cloak
在霍格沃茨潜行时穿的斗篷
that Harry Potter wears to sneak around Hogwarts.
这么"处男"[童话]的解释  我也听不懂
Yeah, I don't speak virgin either.
那枚戒指  会让你变隐形
The ring-- it makes you invisible.
你不是宝贝...[改自指环王]
You're not precious.
很好  你还没睡
Oh, good, you're awake.
泰德
Look, Ted,
有些事我们得谈一谈
there's something we have to talk about.
朋友界线  侵犯隐私
Boundaries? Invasion of privacy?
没收我家的钥匙
Losing your key privileges?
是关于那个20岁的小妞  泰德
It's about the 20-year-old, Ted.
你必须把她上了
You have to bang her.
为了我
For me!
你为什么要我勾搭20岁的女孩
Why do you want me to hook up with this 20-year-old?
你不是很恶心我的行为吗
I thought I disgusted you.
对  不过那是我装的
Yeah, that was all an act.
听我说听我说  我爱罗宾
Look, look, look, I love Robin
我只想和她在一起
and she's the only girl I want to be with.
但是因为常年的一夜情
But my body is detoxing
我的身体还没完全戒掉
after years of one-night stands.
世上也没有戒掉
They don't make gum
一夜情的贴片或口香糖  泰德
or a patch for this, Ted.
但这貌似是个挣大钱的点子
But, hey, billion-dollar idea alert.
好吧  没事
Oh, yeah. That's okay.
我再买一本新的梦之日记
I'll just buy a new dream journal.
你在找什么
What-what-what are you looking for?
你的电话
Your phone.
手机里一定有她的照片吧
There's got to be some pictures of her in here.
我靠  不
Damn it. No.
这些都没用
Those are all worthless.
我需要一夜情的素材  泰德
I need some one-night-stand material, Ted.
这是你妈  你好啊  弗吉尼亚
Oh. Oh. Here's your mom. Hello, Virginia.
我妈可不是一夜情[站]的素材
Um, my mother is not one-night-stand material.
你说得对
Yeah, you're right.
当时不是夜里  我们也不是站着
It wasn't night and we weren't standing.
你们没有"干"嘛吧
That didn't happen.
没  当然没
You're right. It didn't.
你眨眼了
You just winked.
不  我没有
No, I didn't.
你又眨眼了
You just did it again!
行了  总之  我需要你
Look, bottom line: I need you
替我  上了那妞
to proxy bang this girl for me.
做我的替身
Be my stand-in
用你的"小弟"
and put your gland in.
这印在潮帽上应该挺酷
Hey, wow, that'd be good on a hat.
巴尼
Barney,
她只是喜欢我优雅老去的身体
she's just using me for my gracefully aging body.
你挑这个时候来获得自尊吗
You're picking now to get some self-respect?
你曾经假装肖恩・康纳利  骗盲女和你上床
You once banged a blind girl by pretending to be Sean Connery.
苏格兰电影演员  007第一任扮演者
那是你干的
That was you.
没错  那次经历真是滋味无限
Yeah, that conquest was most enjoyable.
抱歉  要勾搭女孩
I'm sorry. T-To hook up with a girl,
我至少得和她有点共同之处吧
I have to connect with her at least a little.
找一个共同之处呗
Then find a connection.
找点简单的
Just go simple.
别找什么奇怪的诗或建筑之类
Nothing about weird poets or buildings
或是任何你取名为《精神粮食》
or any of those stupid articles you've ever e-mailed me
电邮给我的烂文章
with the subject line "Food for thought."
拜托了  泰德
Please, Ted.
你不"上"  我会死啊
I need this.
好吧  你赢了
Fine. You win.
我会上一个20岁的姑娘
I'll bang a hot 20-year-old.
但是我可不会乐在其中
But I'm not gonna enjoy...
骗谁呢
Oh, who am I kidding?
肯定是爽翻了
It's gonna be awesome.
现在  关灯  滚蛋
Now, turn off the lights and go.
别全关掉
Not all the way!
你好  三杯...
Hello. Yeah, three...
纽约本来是全世界最友好
Okay, normally New York is the friendliest,
最住得起的城市
most affordable city in the world.
现在呢  和旧金山一样  又粗鲁又昂贵
Now it's as rude and expensive as San Francisco.
你们说呢
Guys?
这就是订婚后的生活
Oh, hey, that's life once you're engaged.
告诉她吧  宝贝  让她伤心吧
Oh, tell her, baby. Make it hurt.
我去卡座了
I'll be at the booth.
等你来时  我的小内内
My panties may or may not be on
可能在  也可能不在哦
when you get there.
肯定不在了
They won't be!
你们是怎么回事啊
Okay, what is going on with you guys?
是护腕的魔力
It's the cuff.
把我想象成嗑药的蹩脚音乐人
It turns out that picturing me as a loser musician
还有一辆用来偷铜线的破旧货车
with a Vicodin addiction and a beat-up van
让莉莉性趣盎然
I use to steal copper wire really turns Lily's crank.
谁会想得到呢
Who knew?
你的手腕怎么了
Whoa, what-what happened to your wrist?
对护腕过敏了
Oh. It's an allergic reaction.
那就取下来呀
So take it off.
罗宾  一旦为人父母之后
Robin, once you have a child,
只要能换来一点点滚床单的可能性
anything that gets you even remotely close
几个化脓的水泡又算得了什么
to the possibility of sex is worth a few pus-filled blisters.
再疼也胜过我"下半身"煎熬啊
Better the sores weep than I.
等一下  那个小荡货刚进酒吧
Hey, hold on. That slut just got here.
怎么这么快就买到酒了
How'd she get beer already?
你看她手指上有戴订婚戒了吗
Do you see a ring on that finger?
你是说这戒指的隐形作用
Are you saying that this invisibility thing
会害得我以后都没法买到酒了吗
means I might not be able to get beer?
人家才刚刚开始习惯自己买咖啡
I was just getting used to the idea of having to pay for coffee
-贝果圈和付房租呢  -房租啊
- and bagels and rent. - Rent?
现在连一杯酒都买不到
But not being able to get a beer?
我决不接受
Unacceptable.
抱歉
Excuse me.
请为辣妹让一下路
Hot girl coming through.
请给我三杯啤酒
Three beers, please.
靠  我讨厌这戒指
Damn it, ring!
亲爱的
Oh, yeah, baby.
一会记得出去买把弹簧刀
Later you should totally go out and buy a switchblade.
好呀
Sure.
或许爸爸会顺便买些尿布
While I'm out, maybe Daddy picks up some diapers
和微辣的莎莎酱  因为我们无比堕落
and a little mild salsa because we're low.
好吧  你说对了
Well, you're right--
我已经化为无形了
I'm invisible.
那一夜  唯一一个比罗宾还狼狈的人
That night, the only person in worse shape than Robin
是她的未婚夫
was her fiance.
泰德  我快被逼疯了
Ted, I'm desperate.
今天上午  我看到那护腕
Earlier today, I saw that wrist cuff
就给马修买了一副
and I got a partial for Marshall.
你把那妞上了吗
Did you bang that girl yet?
你别激动   也别"鸡"动
Don't get your hopes, or anything else, up.
我试着和她找话题
I tried to connect with her,
可不管说什么
but everything just comes back
最后总是回到她对我年纪的痴迷上去
to her weird fetish about how old I am.
先从简单入手吧  她喜欢看电视吗
Well, j-just go simple-- does she like TV?
不喜欢
No.
但如果我愿意陪你一起看《60分钟》
But I'll watch 60 Minutes with you
美国老牌新闻节目
开多大声看多久都没问题
as loud and as long as you want.
体育呢
Sports?
不喜欢
No.
不过我猜你玩沙壶球时一定帅爆了
But I bet you look super hot playing shuffleboard,
一种老年人常玩的运动
想象你厚厚地涂满止痛药膏的样子
just... slathered in Bengay.
好吧  那她喜欢读书吗
Well, does she like books?
不喜欢
No.
可我猜你一定喜欢
But I bet you do.
你一定有一个又大又厚的...
I bet you have a big, thick
老花眼镜
pair of bifocals.
她这已经不是恋父情节了
She doesn't have daddy issues,
而是恋祖父情节
she has granddaddy issues.
我要和她说再见了
I'm ending it.
泰德  求你了
Ted, I beg of you,
只要她一息尚存  你就不能放弃
don't quit on a body that won't quit.
这句话用来做车标不错
Ooh, ooh, that'll go sweet on a bumper sticker.
我要写在日记上
That's going in the journal.
等等  你偷走了我的梦之日记吗
Wait, did you steal my dream journal?
才没有  好了  在你牙齿落光
No! Now, get back in there before all your teeth fall out
和你在自己高中全校师生面前裸体出演
and you're naked in front of Shaker Heights High School
没排练过的戏剧前  快回去吧
in a play you never rehearsed for.
你个王八蛋
Bastard!
我们之间毫无共通处  绝对要分手了
We don't connect on a single thing. It's over.
不要
It's not...
听着卡莉  我要告诉你
Look, Carly, I got to tell you something.
我们之间不会有未来
I just, I don't see a future here.
我的妈呀
Oh, my God.
你是要死了吗
Are you dying?
真是迷死人了
Oh, that is so hot.
我说  你这是R2-D2的声音吗
Hey... is that R2-D2?
星球大战宇航技工机器人
你喜欢《星球大战》吗
Do you like Star Wars?
我超爱《星球大战》
I love Star Wars.
我也是
Me, too!
虽然我只看过最新的几部
I mean, I've only seen the new ones.
那也成啊
Close enough.
-结果...  -上了
- So? - Yeah.
我就知道  我能感应得到
I knew it! I could feel it.
感觉就跟咱俩一起上了她似的
It's almost like we were hooking up with her together.
你也有同感  对吧
You felt that, right?
要真有这感觉  我就不做了
I couldn't have performed if I did.
你没发现吗  泰德
Don't you see, Ted?
我们俩有兄弟感应啊
We had a bro-nnection.
好了  我得知道她长什么样
All right, I got to know what she looks like--
给我看照片
show me a picture.
一般来说  我不屑于干这种事的
Well, normally, I'm above such things,
但我单身已经很久了  泰德也想炫耀一下
but it's been a while, and, uh, Teddy's braggin'.
好了  这就是她
Okay, here she is.
好  从下往上慢慢看
Okay. Scrolling up.
脚踩"求开垦"高跟鞋  不错不错
Oh, yeah, those are "plow me" Heels. Nice. Uh-huh.
膝盖的瘀痕  让人食指大动
The knee bruise is encouraging.
一路上拉到二十岁的尖峰处
Working our way up to those 20-year-old ta-tas.
哇  地心引力的残酷魔爪
Oh... gravity's cruel grasp
还没有伸向你  我可爱的奇迹翘乳
hasn't found you yet, my sweet perky miracles.
现在  让我们瞧瞧小浪娃的庐山真面目吧
Now, let's get a gander at Dirty Girl's face.
她的脸上写着"欢迎来搞"  对不对
Her face says, "Ready to bone," Am I right?
再重复一次  我说得对不对
I say again, am I right?
这是我同父异母的妹妹
That's my half-sister.
那你还是不要看下一张照片的好
Then you probably shouldn't scroll to the next picture.
天啊
No!
这是我妹啊  泰德
That's my sister, Ted!
问题是  我又不知道
Well, look, I didn't know!
不光是我们  连你都是两年前才知道
None of us even knew you had a sister
你有个同父异母妹妹的
until two years ago, including you!
这不过是奇怪的巧合罢了
This is just some crazy coincidence.
整个纽约市整整4百万女人
There are four million women in the city of New York,
泰德你就偏偏睡了我妹妹
Ted, and you sleep with my sister?
-上天你为什么要这样对我  -我哪知道
- Why would the universe do that to me? - I don't know.
你又没有视女人如弃履过
It's not like you've ever treated women in such a way
"不应该"会招来天谴报应呀
that would invite some sort of karmic retribution.
你睡了我妹妹
You banged my sister!
我可爱的  幼嫩的  无辜的
My sweet, little, innocent...
-她有穿环  -真的吗  在哪里
- Pierced. - Really? Where?
别告诉我
Don't answer that!
现在我知道昨晚我怎么会
Now I know why I felt everything
感应到你对她干的好事了
you did to her last night.
不是什么兄弟感应  是兄妹感应啊
It wasn't a bro-nnection, it was a sis-nnection!
我的天
Oh, my God.
泰德  你有没有
Ted... did you...
超厉害的
Big-time.
有你的  击掌相庆
Nice! High five!
不  等一下
Wait! No! No!
收回击掌
Retraction five!
是你哭着求我帮你上了她的
Hey, hey, you're the one who begged for a proxy bang.
既然我们提到家人这个问题了
And while we're on the subject of family,
我知道你还睡过我妈呢
I'm pretty sure you banged my mom--
妈妈比妹妹严重多了
mom beats sister.
我才没有睡过你妈呢
I never banged your mom.
你刚刚又眨眼了
You just did the winking thing again!
我没有
No, I didn't.
好吧  巴尼  我问你
Fine. Hey, Barney, let me ask you something.
你今天早上有感觉到酸痛吗
Were you, uh, feeling a little sore this morning?
尤其是...
Especially...
友谊到此为止
Friendship over!
好爽
Oh, yeah.
谁是你的吉他兼摩托车手
Who's your guitar-player-biker-
找不到微辣莎莎酱
who-couldn't-find-mild-salsa-
骂句去你的  然后买中辣酱的坏男孩啊
but-said-screw-it- and-went-medium bad boy?
马修  你的手
Marshall, your hand!
好吧  我肯定没有肿成那样
Okay, I'm pretty sure it wasn't that bad,
但马修叔叔讲这件事时总喜欢说成这样
but this is how Uncle Marshall likes to tell the story.
没事  都是护腕弄的
Oh, yeah, no, that's the cuff.
我晕乎乎的  而且也动不了指头
I'm woozy, and I can't flex my fingers...
死鱼的臭味也越来越浓了
...and the rotten fish smell is getting stronger.
但我在学着使用左手
But I'm learning to compensate with my left.
所以说昨晚我要你双掌袭胸
Is that why last night when I asked you to honka honka me
结果你只是一只手上吗
you only honka'd me?
我没想到你会注意到
I didn't think you noticed.
左咪咪嫉妒右咪咪一整天了呢
Snap's been jealous of Crackle all day.
取下护腕吧
Just take the cuff off.
不  宝贝  这样我们就没机会享性福了
No, but, baby, then all the sex will stop.
马修  你不需要戴护腕来让我觉得你性感
Marshall, you don't need a cuff for me to find you sexy.
你只需要冲我微笑
All you have to do is smile,
我就准备好让你扑上来了
and I'm ready for you to hop on Pop.
hop on Pop是著名儿童读物  字面意为跳到爸爸身上来
谢谢  宝贝
Thanks, baby.
你这么晕还能不能坚持最后做一次
Are you too woozy to do it one last time
然后再去看急诊呢
before we seek emergency medical attention?
只有试了才能知道啊
Only one way to find out.
抱歉  兄弟  我的反应太过了
I'm sorry, bro, I totally overreacted.
你觉得呢  我真不敢相信
You think? I can't believe
快递公司居然接受你的死负鼠
you're allowed to ship a dead possum.
它死了吗
He died?
那只负鼠可是我抛给你的橄榄枝[和平]
That possum was supposed to be an olive branch.
你确定它不是在装死吗[负鼠的强项]
Are you sure he's not just playing dead?
它的味道和马修的手一个味儿
He smells like Marshall's hand.
等等  你原谅我了吗
And wait, you-you forgive me?
当然了  我有两根上好雪茄
Absolutely. Hey, I got a couple "Cee-gars."
过来吧
Get over here!
好啦  雪茄拿出来吧
All right. So, where are those "Cee-gars"?
稍后奉上
Eh, we'll break 'em out in a minute.
巴哥
Hey, Barn.
泰德
Ted?
巴尼  你妹妹怎么来了
Barney, what is your sister doing here?
没什么  兄弟  或者我该称呼你为
Nothing, bro. Or should I say,
妹夫
bro-in-law!
恭喜
Congratulations!
你现在要娶我妹妹
You're marrying my sister!
而且你得不惜血本办婚礼  你这个疯子
And you spared no expense, you big crazy!
知道吗  我爱巴尼
You know what? I love Barney,
但戒指的事太令人沮丧了
but this ring thing sucks.
有个恶心的家伙碰到我的胸
Some gross guy just brushed up against my rack
然后向我道歉
and then apologized.
而且我觉得他是真心道歉呢
And I think he really, really meant it.
亲爱的  被陌生人袭胸是件很美滋滋的事
Oh, sweetie, I know it's nice to be groped by strangers,
但没什么比得上那个特别的人
but nothing beats the rush you get
注视你时带给你的悸动
when that one special person looks at you.
真的
It's true.
比如说现在在这个酒吧  我只看得见一个人
Like here in this bar, there's only one thing that I see,
她的面容比世界上任何人
and I see her brighter and more clearly
还要更亮更清晰
than anything else in this world.
知道这是什么吗
You know what that is?
是爱情
That's love.
也有可能是酒精
And possibly alcohol
与非常强效的抗生素产生的效果
mixed with some very powerful antibiotics.
巴尼就是这样看你
And that's how Barney sees you.
我知道你也是这样看巴尼
And I know that's how you see Barney.
婚礼仪式就从
I'd like to start the service
泰德梦境日记中截选的一段开始
with a passage from Ted's dream journal.
"溺水
"Drowning.
渴望空气
Gasping for air.
无处可逃"
No escape."
你梦到了越战吗
Wait, is that about Vietnam?
他梦到了全食超市
It's about Whole Foods.
全美最大天然有机食品零售商
巴尼  我们不会结婚的
Barney. We are not getting married.
超市的过道太窄了
And those aisles are too narrow!
但你们两个必须结婚
But you two have to get married--
否则  你们之间就只是一次廉价
otherwise, it's just a cheap,
无意义  恶心的一夜情
meaningless, disgusting one-night stand.
等等  说清楚下  你是说你反对
Wait, just to be clear, you're saying you're opposed
廉价  无意义  恶心的一夜情吗
to cheap, meaningless, disgusting one-night stands?
是的
Yes.
巴尼  你没明白吗
Barney... don't you see?
你戒瘾成功了
Your detox is done!
你已经戒掉"一夜情瘾"了
You're over one-night stands!
我的天  你说对了
Oh, my God, you're right!
-我自由了  -对
- I'm free! - Yeah.
所以如果你想想  别想得太深刻
So if you think about it-- but not too much--
卡莉和我上床其实是件好事
it's actually good that Carly and I hooked up.
是啊  非常好
Yeah, it's really good.
他的表现就像他还是五十多岁一样
I mean, this guy goes at it like he's still in his 50s.
来根雪茄吧  你这个大疯子
Hey, have a cigar, you big crazy!
别想糊弄过去
Hey, don't try to make this okay.
你还是跟我妹妹上床了
You still slept with my sister.
向我保证你永远不会再这样做
Promise me you will never, ever do that again.
我保证
I promise.
你刚刚眨眼了
You just winked.
我没有
No, I didn't.
-你又眨了  -我没有
- You did it again! - No, I didn't!
你可以保证  对吗
You swear, right?
对  当然了
Yeah. Of course.
那天晚上
That night,
虽然罗宾依然无法拿到啤酒
even though she still couldn't get a beer,
但她了解到戒指的真正魔力
Robin realized the true power of the ring.
罗宾
Hey, Robin.
你弄清楚怎么在订婚的情况下
Did you ever figure out how you're gonna get
从吧台那里拿到喝的了吗
a drink at the bar now that you're engaged?
当然  我知道一个永远有效的方法
Oh, sure. I know a way that's gonna last forever.
威士忌加冰
Scotch on the rocks?
马上来
Coming right up.
在你们对帽子发表看法之前
Now, before you say anything about the hat...
这位妹子的屁屁真是太赞了
this new girl's ass is phenomenal!
马修  你得看看这个
Hey, Marshall, you got to see this.
网购肯定弄混了我的订单
The catalog must have mixed up my order.
你不会相信他们寄给我什么样的牛仔裤
You won't believe the jeans they just sent me.
真滑稽  对吗
Hilarious, right?
绝对的
Totally.
你看起来像是
You look like some
郊区妈妈  开着迷你面包车
suburban mom who drives a minivan
车上全是变味儿的麦圈和空果汁盒
filled with stale Cheerios and empty juice boxes...
有可能
probably makes
用辣椒通心粉和玉米馅饼做晚餐
chili mac and Frito pie for dinner...
车上全是薄荷烟的味道
smells like that menthol cigarette that
她在等着孩子们
she snuck while she was waiting to
冰球训练时  偷偷在车上抽的
pick her kids up from hockey practice.
快过来
Get over here!